DAVID WATTS

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT

davidwattsllegmail.com

0412 957 215

in LinkedIn: @davidwatts11

Github: <u>edaviddigital</u>

EDUCATION

Coder Academy

Diploma of IT, 2022 (Expected)

Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology (RMIT)

Undergraduate Certificate of Computer Science, 2020

Queensland University of Technology (QUT)

Graduate Diploma of Applied Finance, 2015

Swinburne University

Graduate Certificate of Science (Network Systems), 2011

Griffith University

Bachelor of Business (Information Systems), Academic Excellence, 2010

SUMMARY

Emerging software engineer with previous experience in software development teams as a Business Analyst. Started a career change in 2020 by completing an Undergraduate Certificate of Computer Science, followed by a Diploma of IT in web development (bootcamp style) in 2021.

KEY PROJECTS

- <u>Solar Mapper</u> A two-sided marketplace using Ruby on Rails & PostgreSQL, deployed using Heroku.
- <u>Solar App</u> Developed a command line app using Ruby for generating costs and benefits of solar systems.
- <u>dwatts.com.au</u> Used Sass/HTML to develop a responsive portfolio page, deployed using Netlify.
- House Prices a linear regression model using Python
 Jupyter Notebooks for predicting house sale prices.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Business Analyst

IVVY

MAY 2019 - MAR 2021

 Documented and designed new features (billing, payments, CRM, integrations, booking engines) for a web application and event marketplace (<u>ivvy.com</u>).

DAVID WATTS

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript, HTML & Sass/CSS
- Python, Java, Ruby
- Ruby on Rails
- Databases, including PostgreSQL
- React, Express & Node.js (in progress)
- Heroku, Netlify

WORK EXPERIENCE CONT.

Marketing Automation Manager

VILLAGE ROADSHOW OCT 2018 - MAY 2019

 Implemented systems & automated email/SMS journeys utilising Salesforce marketing cloud.

Lead Business Analyst

COMPLY ADVANTAGE FEB 2017 - NOV 2017

- Implemented systems (Salesforce CRM & marketing).
- Lead a team of analysts supporting development of a financial services web application.

Digital Business Analyst / Project Manager

MANTRA GROUP JAN 2016 - OCT 2016

- Documented and designed a new website/accommodation booking engine.
- Implemented email marketing and survey systems.

Technology Graduate to Senior Business Analyst

FEB 2010 - DEC 2015

- Worked in multiple teams as part of Telstra's technology graduate program, including network
- strategy and operations. • Performed analysis for multiple network & IT projects,

planning, commercial analysis, project management,

developing project documents, business cases & financial models.